RG 169:007, Connecticut Forest and Park Association
Connecticut State Library
- Series 12. Photographs, 1900-2011
  - Programs, 1905-2003
    - Trails Day, 1993-2003
      - Various locations and equestrian event, Lebanon, 1996 June 1; Locations include: Torrington, Salmon River, Union, Lebanon, and New Milford. Photographers include: Linda Rapp, Joan Adams, Bob Baldwin, and C. Brooks. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Windsor bike tour, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Arbor Day, Thomas Hooker School, Meriden, 1990 May (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Bird study, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Camp Demonstration Forest, Middle School, Middletown, 2000 May 16 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Camp Forest, Demo Trail and Circuit Area, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) Museum, 1993 June (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Chestnut Stand, Scotland, CT, 1905-1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Chestnut Trials, Manchester, tree farmer, circa 1970 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Demonstration Forest, building of boardwalk, Roving Trails Crew, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Demonstration Forest, classes visiting, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Demonstration Forest, ERT, 1996 July (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Demonstration Forest, Jr Camp, boardwalk, 2000 November 11 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Demonstration Forest, 1997-2000; Folder contains photographs from multiple rolls of film. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Environthon, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Environthon, Kellogg, Derby, New Milford High School, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Environthon, Marborough, 4-H Camp, Coventry team winners-state champions, 1996 May 7-1997 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Environthon, special tree at Minechange, camp property, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Environthon team winners, North West Regional High School, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Environthon training at Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1999 March; Photographs by Ray Taberman. (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Environthon training, Killingworth, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Field Day, 1996 May 11 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Field Day-Forest Stewardship Program, Clinton Land Conservation Trust, 1996 April 27; With Bert Goodwin. (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Field Day-Forest Stewardship Program, Davidson's Field Day, 1995 October 14 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Hall Memorial School, Willington, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Harwinton Consolidated School, 1990 June (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Highland Tree Farm with children, 1988 May (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Highlawn, 1989 June (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Outdoor Study with different groups, circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Project Learning Tree, fifth graders from Portland at Jack Camp's, at Highlawn Tree Farm, 1992 October; Photographs by Linda Rapp. (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Project Learning Tree and Hemlocks PLT writing workshop, 1988-1993 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Project Learning Tree and Hull's Forest Products tour, 1998 May (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Project Learning Tree, instructing, 1987 August (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Project Learning Tree at John Barry School, Meriden, 1998 October (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Project Learning Tree, Lawrence School, Middletown, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Project Learning Tree meeting, undated (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Project Learning Tree workshop, 1998 November (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Read-at-Home program, Goodwin Elementary, Mansfield, 1996 May 20; With Holly-DiBella McCarthy. (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - ReLeaf, Bridgeport, undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - ReLeaf Festival, Bridgeport, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - ReLeaf, Hartford, 1994 May (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - ReLeaf and "Millions of Trees", 1996 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - ReLeaf, Robertson School, Manchester, Woodstock, Hartford, Gales Ferry School, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - New Schoolyard Habitat, Waddell School, Manchester, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - School Yard Habitat, Mary M. Hooker School, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Search project, 1987 July (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Tree Farm program, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Tree Farm dedication, circa 1980 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Tree Farm program, tour, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Tree Farm program, 1980; With Milne. (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Tree Farm program, Sunny Valley, Iron Ore Hill, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Tree Shelter Study, Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station, 1995 October; With Jeff Ward. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Wildlife Habitat, Audubon Center, Sharon and White Memorial, circa 1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - WMA, Session Woods, 1998 April (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Youth Conservation Corps and Hammonasset and other, circa 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Workshops, 1993-2006
    - Backyard Habitat workshop at Session Woods, 1997; With Craig Tufts, NWF. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Black Rock Spring workshop, 2000 April 8 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Black Rock, 2000 April 8; Photographs by Roland. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Black Rock Spring workshop, 2000 April 8; Photographs by JEH (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Bridge building, youth group, 2004 September 30; With Sam Laugeley. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - "Earthways" workshop at Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1998 Fall (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association Field Property, Durham, 2004 April 24; Photographs by Adam Moore. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Food Land and People (FPL) workshop, 1999 January; With Sandee Brown. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Maintainers workshop, Burr Pond State Park, 2000 April 8 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Maintainers Workshop Retreat, Tunxis Trail bridge, 1994 June 5 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Pomeraug Trail, spring workshop, 2002 May (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Project Learning Tree workshop, East Hartford, Glastonbury, Magnet School, 1996 October 16; With Diane Joy. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - School Yard Habitat workshop with NWF, 1999 March 26-27 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Spring trail workshop, Pachaug, 2005 April (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Spring trails workshop/maintenance, Belding WMA, Vernon, 2006 April 29 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Trail maintainers workshop, People's Forest, Barkhamsted, 1996 April 13 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Trail maintainers workshop, People's Forest, 1997 April 1-12 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Trail monitor workshop, 1996 October 5; Photographs by Linda Therrien. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Trails Day workshop, 1993 April 17 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Trail workshop, Charles L. Pack Trail, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Woodcarver's workshop, 2006 April 22 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Events, 1929-2005
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association meeting at the Connecticut Arboretum, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Annual meeting, Rocky Neck, 1986-1991 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting, 1995 April (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting at Highlawn, 1996 June 17 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting, Session Woods, WMA, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting, Kellogg Enviornmental Center, Derby, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting, dedication of Camp Demonstration Forest and Open House, 1999 May-2000 June 6 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Awards, 1989-1999 November 5, 17, 19 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Annual trails dinner and fall programs, 1996 November 1; Photographs by Carol Youell. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Annual trails dinner, 2000 November (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Annual trail meeting awards, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Austin F. Hawes, Memorial Campground, 1968 September (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Awards, Outstanding Community Tree Program-Danbury, Outstanding Urban Forestry Volunteer, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Awards, roving trails crew, 2001 January 4 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Beckley Furnace, field tour, 1998 October; With Walt Landgraff. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Blind Trail dedication, Metropolitan District Commission, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Blue Trails dedication, Chatfield Trail, Cockaponset Trail, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Bookcase, meeting, wedding, undated; Color Negatives only (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Boy Scouts, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Tree Growers at Capitol with Governor Rowland, 1997 April (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Connecticut River Designation Ceremony, 1998 June 29 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut River Ramble, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Cornucopia, University of Connecticut, 1996 September (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Trails dedication, Belding Wildlife Management Area, 1995 June 3 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Trails dedication, Bigelow Hollow State Park, Union, 1995 June 3 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Dedication, Gifford Pinchot Monument, 2000 August 11 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Dedication for James Spignes Wildlife Management Area and Scholarship Fund, 1999 June 22 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Dedication of Natural Area Preserves, Haddam, 1999 April 26 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Dedication of Rhododendrum Sanctuary Trails, 1995 June-1999; Photographs by John Olsen. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Dinosaur State Park, Reopening and McLean Game Refuge, 1996 June 30 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - EFNE Awards, 1999 October 7 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut environment protection, 2004 March 23 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Field meeting and other special occasions, circa 1980 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Field meeting at a tree farm, 1991 September 26 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Field meeting, Harry A. McKusick Memorial Stone, Nathan Hale State Forest, 1973 September 29 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Field meeting, southeast Connecticut with Connecticut Forest and Park Association, circa 1972 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Field meeting, Tobey Bog at Great Mountain Forest, undated (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Forestry field meeting at Pleasant Valley, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Forest Stewardship Tour and ECFLA, Ed Wyman and Chuck Lee property, 1995 May 15; With Dan Donahue, Forester. (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Gateway Inspection, Connecticut River National Scenic Area, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - George Milne Award, Hebron, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Goodwin Scholarship, welcome for recipients at Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Greenway, undated (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Greenway Awards, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Greenway Awards ceremony at State Capitol with Governor Rowland, 1999 January 11; Photographs by Linda Therrien. (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Greenways Conference in Rhode Island, 1999; Folder includes photographs of Connecticut and Rhode Island governors. (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Hammonasset opening, 1993 Summer (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Heritage Advisory Board meeting, 1994 August 2 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Hearing in North Stonington on nuclear waste, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Heritage river announcement, 1998 June (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Les Corey dinner, circa 1980 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Loggers meeting, forester certification training, 1995; Photographs by Carole Youell. (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - L and W Conservation Fund, Leiberman's visit, 1999 August (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Maple syrup operation, spring 1986 issue (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Mayor's Walk, Case Mountain, 1973 September 30 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - National Urban Forest Conference, New York City, 1995 September (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Open space presentation and legislation dedication at Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1998 June (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Outstanding TF, Gillette Castle, 1994 October (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Pachaug State Forest, field meeting and forestry, 1971-1979 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Peoples Forest dedication, Matthies Trail, 1929 October (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Peoples Forest with "Harry the Hiker", 75th anniversary celebration, 1999 October 17 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Peoples Forest rededication with "Harry the Hiker", 1999 October 19 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Connecticut Pilot Round Table for 7th American Forest Congress, 1995 July (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Volunteer of the year, 2001 June; Presentation of certificate (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Ragged Mountain, opening and dedication of and tri state area, 1980 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Ray Larsen Event, Laughing Brook, 2000-2001 January 4; Dr. Ray Larson and family at a log cabin and Tree Farmer of the Year 2000. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut ReLeaf Tree Festival, Fairfield, 1996 May 14 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut ReLeaf Festival, Fairfield, 1996 May 14; Photographs by Carol Youell. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut ReLeaf Tree Festival, Fairfield, St. Brendon's School-Poster Winner-Arbor Day, 1996 May 14; Photographs by Carol Youell. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut ReLeaf Festival, Fairfield, 1996 May 14; Photographs by Carol Youell. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Speakers and awards, headquarters, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Sport show, circa 1960-1970 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Spring meeting, 1933 June 3 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - State Employees Campaign Kickoff, 1994 September (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Tagging, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Telcom Conference, panel discussion, 1998 December 3 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Trails Day, committee meeting, 1995-2000 May 17 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Trails Day, Handicaped Trails Day Event-North Windham, Bolton Mountain Bike Event, Charter Oak Greenway-Manchester/East Hartford, 1996 June 1; Photographs by John Hibbard. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Trails dinner, 1996 November 1 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Trails dinner and trails workers, circa 1987 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Trails dinner, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Trails Day pot-luck dinner, 2000 June 3 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Trails day pot-luck supper and other events, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Trails supper, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Trails for Tomorrow winners honored, 1995 August (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Trail Town Awards, 1996 September (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Trail Town Awards, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Tree farm, Tree Farmers of the Year, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Tree farm, Tree Farmer of the Year Award, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Tree farm meeting with award photographs, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Tree walk with Ed Richardson, Long Lane, Middletown, 1998 May 30 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Walk on City of Bristol, Water Department, W.S. lands with Jody Rowlands, 1999 October 16 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Wine tasting, 1998 December (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Clubs, Associations and Organizations, 1938-2000
    - 7th American Forest Congress, Washington, D.C., 1996 February (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station, hurricane damage, 1938; Photographs by Walter O. Filley. (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Connecticut Conservation Conference, 1950 November 16; under the auspices of the Natural Resources Council of Connecticut, Hotel Bond, Hartford, Connecticut (Box 44)
    - Connwood Foresters, Incorporated, 1989-1994 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Christmas trees and Christmas Tree Growers Association, 1970-1982 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Christmas Tree Growers Association, 40th anniversary, 2000 Fall (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Friends of State Parks, Governor and Mrs. Rowland, 1996 April (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Hull's Mill, 1998 October 23 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Maine Forest Products Mill and PLT, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Recreation and National Heritage Trust Advisory Board Awards, circa 1993 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Shaker Pines Forestry Corporation, undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Sleepy Giant Park Association, 1968-1992 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Jones Tree Farm with children, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Tree farm, Hickory Ridge Tree Farm, circa 1970 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Tree farm, Highlawn and Jack Camp, circa 1976 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Tree farm, Iron Ore Hill, circa 1970 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - The National Urban Forestry Group, tour of Hartford-led by Ed Richardson, Busnell Park, Elizabeth Park, school, 1999 June (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Norwich Free Academy Outing Club, Rhodendron Santuary, Pachaug State Forest, Voluntown, 1999 June 8 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Buildings, 1960-1999
    - Austin F. Hayes, Memorial Campground, 1968 January (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Landscaping at headquarters, circa 1980; Folder includes a photograph negative disc. (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Headquarters, construction and dedication of James Goodwin Center, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Headquarters, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Headquarters, Goodwin Center under construction and after occupancy, 1985-1989 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Headquarters, dedication of James L. Goodwin Center, entrance to James L. Goodwin State Forest, 1960-1986; Folder includes photographs of Mrs. Goodwin. (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Headquarters, 1989, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Headquarters, landscaping, 1999 January-May (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Hemlocks Conference Facility, 1994 May (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Kellogg Enviornmental Center, Derby, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Topsmeade, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Landscapes, 1930-2001
    - Aerial, Housatonic and Naugatuck at Derby and Shelton, circa 1974; Photographs by Virgina Welch. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Aerial view, unknown location, 1995 April 20 (Box 44)
    - Bluff Point, aerial views, 1958; Photographs by John Hibbard. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture, circa 1960 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Big trees, 1990 May-1994 June (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Bluff Point, aerial views, 1958; Photographs by John Hibbard. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Christmas trees and Christmas Trees Growers Association, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Errosion-sediments control, Middletown Watershed Area, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Fort Griswold, 1964 July (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Frosted Colorado Blue Spruces, Prospect, 1979 February; Parsonage Congregational Church; Michael Pochan Collection; 2 framed color photographs (Box 44)
    - Gaylordsville, Washington Oak, 1990 October; Photographs by G. Dreyer. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Merritt Parkway, circa 1970 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Mount Higby, Middletown, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Mountain, 1930 November 20 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Nature, circa 1988 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Nature, flowers, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Naugatuck, Route 63, 1968-1969; Photographs by David M. Smith. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Overlook, circa 1990 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Oversized post cards, 4 seasons in Vermont, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Pests of forest, damage to forest and trees, circa 1980 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Southford Falls, 1965 July (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Salt marsh, Tokeneke, Darien-Scott's Cove and Five Mile River, Riverside-Amundsen's Boatyard, undated; Photographs used for Woodlands cover. (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Snow shots, 1990-2001 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Stoddard Hill, 1964 September (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Tornado damage, Hamden, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Water, 1960-1999 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Westuds, 1991 April-1992 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - West Woods, Guilford, 1971 February 24 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Wetland, undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Wetlands of Guilford, Conover property - East River marsh area, 1965 September 16; Gift to Audobon Society of Coastal Connecticut (Box 44)
    - White Memorial, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Cliffs, 1930 November 9; Two displays/broken in half, shows cliffs and possibly rockslide, roadsign reads 5 ton bridge (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Washington Oak, Giant Sycamore of Cheshire, Energy crisis is contained - firing up the boiler with sawdust., circa 1950; Label on back of both tree photos reads Mr. & Mrs. Michael Pochan of Guilford, CT; 3 mounted color photos (Box 48)
  - Exhibits and Display Materials, 1930-2005
    - Arbor Day, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Blue-Blazed Trails, undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Cards, 1989-1998 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Fire truck and possibly Civillian Conservation Corps Camp, circa 1930 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Gathering and hike, undated (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Headquarters, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Legislative Office Building display, 1995 December (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Logs, undated (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Maintenance and fishing, various activities and places, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Photo exhibit-1991, various subjects, Mohawk Mountain, Mattatuck Trail, 1988-1993 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Photocopies of photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Photographs for Connecticut Forest Recreation Guide, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Photographs from ReLeaf, awards, other, undated (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Prints made from old photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - ReLeaf, undated (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - State Parks and State Forest, various locations, 1940-1977 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Trails-volunteers, Pachaug State Forest-Voluntown, Black Rock State Park, Cromwell Meadows State Park, Bigelow Hollow State Park, 2002-2007 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Trees, undated (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Work parties, activities, 1990-2005 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - New England Natural Areas project, 1971; Each poster displays photographs, map, and reporting form documenting reasons the area merits protection as a natural area. The areas are Bald Peak Summit in Salisbury - a mica schist block; Brazos Quarries in Portland - abandonded brownstone quarries and dinosaur footprints; Cromwell Road Cut in Cromwell - Triassic rocks; Glastonbury Meadows in Glastonbury - meander in Connecticut River floodplain; Poquetanuck Cove in Preston/Ledyard - fish spawning area; The Great unconformity in Southington - rocks formed in different historical periods; 6 posters (Box 48)
  - Publication Materials, 1913-2001
    - Appalachian Adventure, book order, undated (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Brochure, Life Membership Brochure film, undated (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Brochure-new membership and photographs used for brochure from various locations, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Connecticut geological, soils, forest, charcoal kilns from article by Henry Hicock, 1913-1970; Folder also contains maps. (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - Early photographs, 1965-1975 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Effects of highway widening in Bridgewater, Route 133, 1965-1970 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - Farmland article photographs, 2001 April 13 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - Footprints, dinosaur tracks, natural forest vegetation maps, 1956-1970 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Highways, circa 1950; Shows early model cars. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association history, circa 1920-1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association, printing layout, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Illustrations and photographs, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Cover art, undated; Possibly used for canvas bags for year end appeal incentive, includes mockups and logos. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Project learning tree workshop application, undated; two layouts with overlays, possibly used for brochure (Box 48)
    - Logos, circa 1994-1995, undated
      - Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Connecticut Grown, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - EMS, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Funder logos, circa 1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Greenways, circa 1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - ReLeaf, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Yankee Energy, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - March is sugaring-off time, Year of the Forest Newsletter, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - National Trails Day layout, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Overlay-state of Connecticut, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)